Guide to the Richard Smalley papers, 1943-2007, bulk 1990-2005 MS 490
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Lectures, Presentations, and Conferences, 1994 - 2002; 249504
  - National Science Foundation Distinguished Lectures in the Mathematical and Physical Sciences, "Buckyballs and Nanotechnology", May 25-27, 1994; 249584 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - American Chemical Society (Greater Lakes-Central Regional Meetings), "Carbon's Role in Nanotechnology (Both Wet and Dry)", June 1, 1994; 249583 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Gordon Research Conference, High Temperature Chemistry of Advanced Materials, "In Search of Fullerene Fibers", August 3, 1994; 249582 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Symposium on Quantum Theory of Real Materials, "Field Emission and Growth of Fullerene Tubes and Fibers", August 13, 1994; 249581 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - National Research Council Canada, "The Future of Spectroscopy: from Astronomy to Biology", September 25-28, 1994; 249580 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Office of Naval Research, Solid State and Surface Chemical Science and Technology Review, "Carbon Nanotubes and Nanofibers", September 28-30, 1994; 249579 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Sixteenth Annual Meeting of the Council for Chemical Research, "Fullerenes and the Challenge of Nanotechnology", October 3, 1994; 249578 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Fourth International Symposium on Applied Chemistry, "Buckyballs and Nanotechnology", October 20-21, 1994; 249577 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Welch Foundation, Chemical Dynamics of Transient Species, October 24-25, 1994; 249576 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - American Chemical Society (Rochester Section), Harrison Howe Award, "Field Emission and Growth of Fullerene Nanotubes", "C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-based Nanotechnology", November 9, 1994; 249575 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Monsanto Company, Technical Community of Monsanto, "C 60 and the Emerging Carbon-Based Nanotechnology", November 17, 1994; 249574 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Materials Research Society Symposium G, Science and Technology of Fullerene Materials,"Field Emission and Growth of Fullerene Nanotubes", November 28-December 2, 1994; 249573 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - American Chemical Society (North Alabama Section), Madison Marshall Award, "Buckyballs and Nanotechnology", January 25, 1995; 249572 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - National Science Foundation Instrumentation for Materials Research Review Panel, January 31, 1995; 249571 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Society of Rice University Women Seminar, "Nanotechnology at Rice", March 6, 1995; 249570 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Fermi National Accelerator Laboratory, "Buckyballs and Nanotechnology", March 10, 1995; 249569 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Houston Intellectual Law Association, "Nanotechnology and the Future", April 13, 1995; 249568 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Duke University Chemistry Dept, "The Nanowire Challenge", May 5, 1995; 249567 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Stanford University Chemistry Dept, Stauffer Lecture Series, "On the Birth and Death of Nanotubes", "Buckyballs and Nanotechnology", May 10-12, 1995; 249566 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Fullerenes: Chemistry, Physics and New Directions Symposium VII, "Field Emission from an Atomic Wire", May 21-26, 1995; 249565 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Princeton Reunions '95 Graduate Alumni Day Forum, "Novel Materials and Their Impact on Our Future", May 26, 1995; 249564 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Union Carbide Research and Development Presentation, "Carbon Nanotubes and Nanoprobes", May 31-June1, 1995; 249563 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - University of Chicago Honorary Degree: Doctor of Science, June 8-9, 1995; 249562 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - NATO Advanced Research Workshop, The Chemical Physics of Fullerenes: 10(5) Years Later, "Unraveling Nanotubes: Field Emission from an Atomic Wire", June 12-16, 1995; 249561 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - University of Cologne Chemistry Dept, Alder Lecture, "Buckyballs and Nanotechnology", June 18-20, 1995; 249560 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory Molecular Design Institute Meeting, "Tubes", July 5-6, 1995; 249559 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Dr. Alfred Bortz Interview, To the Young Scientist (Chapter), "Buckyball Science on a Roll", July 17, 1995; 249558 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Rohm & Haas Technology Panel, August 9, 1995; 249557 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 35th IUPAC (International Union of Pure and Applied Chemistry) Congress, "Fullerene Nanowires", August 14-19, 1995; 249556 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - NATO Advanced Research Workshop on Modular Chemistry, September 9-12, 1995; 249555 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Dartmouth College 28th Annual Camille and Henry Dreyfus Lectures, "The Dry Side of Nanotechnology", September 26-28, 1995; 249554 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - C, Soot, and Sun: French-American Workshop, "Fullerenes from Sunlight", October 8-12, 19995; 249553 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Welch Foundation 39th Conference on Chemical Research, Nanophase Chemistry, "Chemistry of Clusters", October 23-24, 1995; 249552 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Carroll College Chemistry Seminar, "The Dry Side of Nanotechnology", October 30, 1995; 249551 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - NASA International Conference on Integrated Micro-Nanotechnology for Space Applications, October 30-November 3, 1995; 249550 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - University of Wisconsin at Madison, John E. Willard Lectures, "Field Emission and Growth of Fullerene Nanotubes", "The Dry Side of Nanotechnology", October 31-November 2, 1995; 249549 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 4th Foresight Conference on Molecular Nanotechnology, "Nanotechnology at Rice", November 9-11, 1995; 249548 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Arizona State University, Eyring Lectures in Chemistry and Biochemistry, "The Dry Side of Nanotechnology", "Field Emission and Growth of Fullerene Nanotubes", November 13-15, 1995; 249547 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - New York University Dept of Chemistry, "The Dry Side of Nanotechnology", December 1, 1995; 249546 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - University of Dallas Board of Councillors, "On the Dry Side of Nanotechnology", "Nanotechnology and the Next 50 Years", December 7, 1995; 249545 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Presentations List, 1996; 249544 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - American Institute of Chemical Engineers (South Texas Chapter), "From Balls to Tubes to Ropes: New Materials from Carbon", January 4, 1996; 249543 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Office of Naval Research,Solid State, Surface, and Organometallic Chemistry Workshop, "Continuous Growth of Single-Wall Nanotubes (Cancelled), January 9-12, 1996; 249542 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Rice University Summit of the Minds: Brown Society and Lovett Society, "Nanotechnology on the Dry Side", February 3, 1996; 249541 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - University of Florida Gainsville Chemistry Dept, "From Balls to Tubes to Ropes: New Materials from Carbon", March 6-7, 1996; 249540 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Florida State University Chemistry Dept, "Why Atoms Stick Together", March 7-9, 1996; 249539 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - HTS Workshop on Physics, Materials, and Applications, "Nanoscience and Technology", March 14, 1996; 249538 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Scientia: Approaching the Millenium, "Nanotechnology and the Next 50 Years", March 19, 1996; 249537 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Clements High School Organic Chemistry Class, March 26, 1996; 249536 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - ACS: Undergraduate Chemistry Research Symposium (Rice Chapter), April 13, 1996; 249535 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Kilby Awards Foundation, April 20, 1996; 249534 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Center for Nanoscale Science and Technology Groundbreaking Ceremony, "Nanoscale Science", April 30, 1996; 249533 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Franklin Institute Awards, 1996 Franklin Medal, "Nanotechnology and the Next 50 Years", May 1-3, 1996; 249532 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - International Symposium on Fullerene Chemistry, "From Balls to Tubes to Ropes: New Materials from Carbon", May 5-9, 1996; 249531 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Northeastern University, 30th Annual Arthur D. Little Lecture, "From Balls to Tubes to Ropes: New Materials from Carbon", "Nanotechnology and the Next 50 Years", May 15-16, 1996; 249530 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Engineering, Science, and Technology Council of Houston, Achievement in Science Award, "Nanotechnology and the Next 50 Years", May 17, 1996; 249529 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - International Vacuum Electron Sources Conference (IVESC 96), "Field Emission from an Atomic Wire" (cancelled), July 1-2, 1996; 249528 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - International Symposium on Small Particles and Inorganic Clusters (ISSPIC 8) (cancelled), July 1-6, 1996; 249527 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Fullerenes '96 Conference, "Chrystalline Ropes of Metallic Carbon Nanotubes", July 7-10, 1996; 249526 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Rice University Advanced Placement Summer Institute Chemistry Course, July 31, 1996; 249525 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Northwestern University JRDC-NU International Workshop on PI- Electron Materials, "Chrystalline Ropes of Metallic Carbon Nanotubes", August 13-14, 1996; 249524 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - ACS Chemical Education Group & the University of Pittsburgh Chemistry Dept, "Nanotechnology and the Next 50 Years", September 19, 1996; 249523 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - University of Pittsburgh Chemistry Dept, "From Balls to Tubes to Ropes: New Materials from Carbon", September 20, 1996; 249522 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Office of Naval Research, Materials Sciences Division, MDI Progress Meeting, October 2-3, 1996; 249521 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - University of Connecticut Institute of Materials Science, IMS Distinguished Lecture, "From Balls to Tubes to Ropes: New Materials from Carbon", October 9, 1996; 249520 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Ohio State University, 1996 Evans Award Lecture, "Tubes for Tips: Touching and Feeling on the Nanometer Scale", "From Balls to Tubes to Ropes: New Materials from Carbon", October 10-12, 1996; 249519 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - National Science Foundation Board Meeting, October 16-18, 1996; 249518 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Welch Foundation, Chemistry on the Nanometer Scale, October 21-22, 1996; 249517 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Princeton University 250th Anniversary, Chemistry Symposium: Between Matter and Life, "From Molecules to Materials:Fullerenes from Balls to Tubes"; Physics Conference: Critical Problems in Physics, October 30-November 2, 1996; 249516 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - After Hours Network of Houston, November 19, 1996; 249515 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Greater Southwest Houston Chamber of Commerce, November 19, 1996; 249514 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - White House/Swedish Embassy Events Honoring 1996 Nobel Prize Winners, November 21, 1996; 249513 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - The Nobel Prize in Chemistry, "Discovering the Fullerenes", December 10, 1996; 249512 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Dover Club Breakfast Presentation, December 20, 1996; 249511 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Office of Naval Research, Carbon Nanotubes: Opportunities, Requirements, and Challenges, May 30-June 1, 1997; 249510 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - NASA and SAIC, Nanospace 98: To the Planets and Beyond, "Application of Fullerenes and Carbon Nanotubes in Engineering the Thermal Conduction Properties of Composite Systems", November 1-6, 1998; 249509 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Materials Research Society Symposium, Carbon Nanotubes, Fullerenes, and Related Carbon Materials, "Buckytubes: New Materials and Devices from Carbon", November 30, 1998; 249508 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - NASA Nanospace 2000: Advancing the Human Frontier, Expert Panel on Nanotechnology, January 23-28, 2000; 249507 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - NASA Nanospace 2001: Exploring Interdisciplinary Frontiers, Keynote Speaker, March 13-16, 2001; 249506 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Nanospace 2002: Future Technology Frontiers, June 24-28, 2002; 249505 (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Series VIII: Nanotechnology and Nanohealth at Rice University, 1993-2005; 249494
  This series contains materials on Nanotechnology and Nanohealth projects at Rice University.
  - Nanotechnology Committee Correspondence, Outgoing, 1993-1995; 249503 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Nanotechnology Committee Correspondence, Incoming, 1993-1994; 249502 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Nanotechnology Committee Reading List, 1994; 249501 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Rice Nanotechnology Colloquium Series, 1994-1996; 249500 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Proposal for Center for Carbon Nanotechnology NSF Science and Technology Center, September 1998; 249499 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Alliance for Nanohealth Operating Agreement, White Paper, Aims, and FAQ, 2004-2005; 249498 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Alliance for Nanohealth Correspondence, 2003-2005; 249497 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Articles and Brochures on Nanohealth, 2001-2005, n.d.; 249496 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - World's Largest Nanotube Model Event, April 22, 2005; 249495 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Series IX: Reprints and Articles, 1973-2003; 249490
  This series contains versions of articles and reprints of Dr. Smalley's publications.
  - Reprints, 1973-1981; 249493 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Reprints, 1982-1986; 249492 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Reprints, 1987-2003; 249491 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Series X: Areas of interest/research, 1995-2004; 249482
  This series includes papers on conferences and projects of interest to Dr.Smalley, but in which he did not serve in any official capacity.
  - NASA International Conference on Integrated Micro/Nanotechnology for Space Applications, October 30-November 3, 1995; 249489 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Proceedings of the NASA International Conference on Integrated Micro/Nanotechnology for Space Applications Part I, October 30-November 3, 1995; 249488 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Proceedings of the NASA International Conference on Integrated Micro/Nanotechnology for Space Applications Part II, October 30-November 3, 1995; 249487 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Rice Alliance for Technology and Entrepreneurship Workshop, October 11-12, 2002; 249486 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Strategic Partnership for Research in Nanotechnology, Nanotech for Air Warfare Handouts, December 15-16, 2003; 249485 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Project Buckeye, 1997-1998; 249484 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Texas-UK Collaborative Initiative in Bioscience, 2003-2004; 249483 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Series XI: Copies of Research Notebooks, 1984-2005; 249463
  Restrictions
  The copies of Dr. Smalley's research notes are restricted. Permission to view these materials must be obtained from the Rice University Office of the General Counsel.
  - Research Notebook #3, January 1984-December 1986; 249481 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Research Notebook #4, January 1, 1988-June 1, 1990; 249480 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Research Notebook #5, July 1, 1990-September 1, 1993; 249479 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Research Notebook #6, April 19, 1994-November 22, 1994; 249478 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Research Notebook #7, November 22, 1994-September 8, 1995; 249477 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Research Notebook #8, September 10, 1995-April 21, 1996; 249476 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Research Notebook #9, April 21, 1996-August 23, 1996; 249475 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Research Notebook #10, August 23, 1996-April 10, 1997; 249474 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Research Notebook #11, April 11, 1997-July 9, 1997; 249473 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Research Notebook #12, July 9, 1997-October 21, 1997; 249472 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Research Notebook #13, October 21, 1997-January 7, 1999; 249471 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Research Notebook #14, January 7, 1999-September 15, 1999; 249470 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Research Notebook #15, September 17, 1999-June 22, 2000; 249469 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Research Notebook #16, June 23, 2000-January 17, 2001; 249468 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Research Notebook #17, January 17, 2001-January 29, 2002; 249467 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Research Notebook #18, February 1, 2002-February 21, 2005; 249466 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Research Notebook #19, February 22, 2005-July 10, 2005; 249465 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Research Notebook #20, July 10, 2005-September 12, 2005; 249464 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Series XII: Chemistry 151 Lecture Notes, Problem Sets, and Exams, 1998; 249458
  - Chem 151 General Information, 1998; 249462 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Chem 151 Problem Sets and Exams, 1998; 249461 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Chem 151 Lecture Notes I, 1998; 249460 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Chem 151 Lecture Notes II, 1998; 249459 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Series XIII: Lectures, Presentations, and Conferences, 1997-2005; 249265
  - Senator Phil Gramm press briefing on the National Research Investment Act, March 14, 1997; 249457 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - IWFAC '97 (cancelled), June 29-July 5, 1997; 249456 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - American Carbon Society, 249455 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 3rd International Conference on Materials Chemistry (cancelled), July 21-25, 1997; 249454 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Bell Labs General Research Colloquium Distinguished Lecture Series: "Buckeytubes/New Materials and New Devices from Carbon", July 31-August 1, 1997; 249453 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Halliburton presentation, September 9, 1997; 249452 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - CNST Luncheon, Setember 11, 1997; 249451 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - West Point Society of Greater Houston luncheon, September 12, 1997; 249450 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - NASA Ames Director's Colloquium, September 25, 1997; 249449 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Houston Image Group, September 29, 1997; 249448 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Phillips Petroleum:"The Future of the Fullerenes", September 30, 1997; 249447 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratories Director's Colloquium (cancelled), October 7, 1997; 249446 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - National Science Board Convocation (cancelled), October 9, 1997; 249445 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - SACNAS National Conference, October 11, 1997; 249444 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - University of Pennsylvania Advancing the Frontiers of Condensed Matter Science Symposium: "The Future of Fullerenes", October 13-14, 1997; 249443 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Rohm & Haas Science Group: "Buckeytubes!", October 15, 1997; 249442 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - St. John's University (cancelled), October 17, 1997; 249441 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - American Chemical Society (cancelled), October 18, 1997; 249440 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 5th Foresight Conference on Molecular Nanotechnology: "Buckeyballs and Buckeytubes: Fullerence Pieces of a Future Nanotechnology", November 5-9, 1997; 249439 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - University of Michigan Honorary Degree, December 14, 1997; 249438 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - IBM, December 17, 1997; 249437 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Bernard M. Oliver Symposium on the Future (cancelled), January 8, 1998; 249436 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Southwest Research Institute Lecture "Buckeytubes: New Materials and New Devices from Carbon", January 12, 1998; 249435 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - American Chemical Society (cancelled), January 23, 1998; 249434 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - University of Colorado, Boiulder Chemical Physics Colloquium (cancelled), January 29-30, 1998; 249433 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Wiess School of Natural Sciences External Review, February 5-6, 1998; 249432 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (cancelled), February 15, 1998; 249431 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - George B. Kistiakowsky Lecture: "Buckytubes: New Materials and New Devices from Carbon", February 24, 1998; 249430 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - 12th International Winterschool on Electronic Properties of Novel Materials, February 28-March 7, 1998; 249429 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - American Physical Society (cancelled), MArch 16-20, 1998; 249428 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Advanced Light Source Workshop (cancelled), March 23-24, 1998; 249427 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - DARPA and Lockheed meetings, March 24-25, 1998; 249426 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Rice Alumni College: "Buckyballs and Buckytubes: New Materials and New Devices from Carbon", March 27, 1998; 249425 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - American Chemical Society Meeting: "Buckytubes: New Materials/Nanotechnology", March 29, 1998; 249424 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Materials Technology Consortium Conference (ASM), April 7, 1998; 249423 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - 8th Annual F.E. Bartell Memorial Lecture (cancelled), April 9, 1998; 249422 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Kiwanis Club of Houston, April 15, 1998; 249421 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - University of Houston Frontier of Condensed Matter Physics Symposium: "Buckytubes: New Materials and New Devices from Carbon", April 30, 1998; 249420 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Dow Materials Technical Advisory Board: "Buckytubes and Fibers: New Materials for Technology", May 9, 1998; 249419 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Electric Power ResearchnInstitute Workshop, May 13-14, 1998; 249418 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - South Texas High School Students, June 3, 1998; 249417 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Department of Defense High Performance Computation Users Group Meeting: "Fullerenes, Tubes and Fibers", June 3, 1998; 249416 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Swedish Consulate National Day, June 7, 1998; 249415 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Sematech Distinguished Seminar: "Horizons of Nanotechnology", June 12, 1998; 249414 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - 21st Army Science Conference, June 15, 1998; 249413 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Milby High School Students, June 17, 1998; 249412 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Society of Women Engineers Convention: "The Future of the Fullerenes", June 19, 1998; 249411 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Gorden Conference Nanofab GRC, June 21-26, 1998; 249410 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Future Memory Options Conference, June 29, 1998; 249409 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - International Conference on Science and Technology of Synthetic Materials (cancelled), JUly 12-18, 1998; 249408 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Berkeley Lab, July 17-19, 1998; 249407 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Princeton Chemistry Seminar: "The Future of the Fullerenes", September 25, 1998; 249406 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - NSF Advisory Committee (cancelled), October 14-16, 1998; 249405 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Instrument Society of America: "Buckytubes: New Materials and New Devices from Carbon", October 21, 1998; 249404 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Teach for America, October 22, 1998; 249403 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - NASA Nanospace '98, November 3, 1998; 249402 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - National Chemistry Week, November 4, 1998; 249401 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - NASA-JSC AAA National Conference, November 11, 1998; 249400 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Symposium on Reporting Science in the 21st Century (cancelled), March 19, 1999; 249399 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Approaches to Combat Terrorism: Opportunities for Basic Research, November 19-21, 2002; 249398 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Intel Corporation, informal discussion, January 7-8, 2003; 249397 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Partners in Science National Conference, "Nanotechnology, Energy, and the Science and Technology Workforce", January 17-18, 2003; 249396 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - MIT Forum, January 22, 2003; 249395 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Nanomaterials for Aerospance Symposium dinner, January 27-30, 2003; 249394 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Basic Energy Sciences Advisory (BESAC) meeting, February 25-26, 2003; 249393 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Centennial Exhibition of the Nobel Prize, February 3, 2003; 249392 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - The Bridge Group, "Nanotechnology and the Energy Challenge", February 14, 2003; 249391 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Business-Civic Leadership Forum, February 21, 2003; 249390 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Nanotechnology in Texas (cancelled), February 26, 2003; 249389 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - DOE Nanoscale Science Research Centers (NSRC) Worshop, "Carbon Based Nanostructures", February 26-28, 2003; 249388 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - CBEN Nanotechnology Seminar, February 28, 2003; 249387 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - NASA/Rice Workshop SWNT Growth Mechanisms, "Growing Them Longer and Stronger", February 28-March 2, 2003; 249386 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - President's Council of Advisors on Science and Technology (PCAST), March 2-3, 2003; 249385 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Hydrogen Storage Think Tank, March 13-14, 2003; 249384 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - University of Houston Distinguished Lecturer Series, March 17, 2003; 249383 (Box 10, Folder 79)